Transcript and translation
from http://youtu.be/B_dGHjK_yk8
Sung by Park Hye-Na (박혜나)
The snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
하얀 눈 뒤덥인 산 위에
hayan nun dwideopin san wie
Over the white snow capped mountains
not a footprint to be seen
발자국 하​나 업구​나
baljaguk ha​na eopgu​na
there are no footprints
A kingdom of isolation,
그 누구도 엄는 왔국
geu nugudo eomneun wangguk
This empty kingdom
and it looks like I'm the queen
내가 이곧 여 왔이야
naega igot yeo wangiya
I'm the queen here
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
내 안에 분은 바람 거친 폭풌을
nae ane buneun baram geochin pokpungeul
A violent wind storm blows within me
Couldn't keep it in, heaven knows I tried
마ᄀ​을 수 어ᄇᄉ​어 애를 썯잊암안
mag​eul su eobs​eo aereul sseotijaman
Couldn't stop it, though I tried...
Don't let them in, don't let them see
매움 열짐아 들킺임아
maeum yeoljima deulkijima
Don't open your heart, don't be discovered
Be the good girl you always had to be
착한 모습 언제​나 보여​줌여
chakhan moseup eonje​na boyeo​jumyeo
Always display a good image
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
철저하게 숨겯는데
cheoljeohage sumgyeotneunde
Though I hid it thoroughly...
Well, now they know!
들켜 버렸​어
deulkyeo beoryeoss​eo
... it was bound to be discovered!
Let it go, let it go!
다 잊어 다 잊어
da ijeo da ijeo
Forget it all, forget it all!
Can't hold it back any more!
이젠 참지 않을 거야
ijen chamji anheul geoya
Now I'm done holding back
Let it go, let it go!
다 잊어 다 잊어
da ijeo da ijeo
Forget it all, forget it all!
Turn away and slam the door!
문을 열고 나 아갈 거야
muneul yeolgo na agal geoya
I'll open the door and go
I don't care what they're going to say
괜찮아 누가 뭐라해도
gwaenchanha nuga mwerahaedo
It's alright, no matter what anyone says
Let the storm rage on
폭풌 모라쳐도
pokpung morachyeodo
Though the storm rages on
The cold never bothered me anyway.
추위 따윈 두렵지 않다​네
chuwi ttawin duryeopji anda​ne
I'm not afraid of the cold.
It's funny how some distance
거리를 두고 보면
georireul dugo bomyeon
If you look from a distance,
Makes everything seem small
모든게 작아 보여
modeunge jaga boyeo
everything seems small
And the fears that once controlled me
나를 두렵게 핻던 걷들
nareul duryeopge haetdeon geotdeul
Now I'm not afraid of ...
Can't get to me at all!
이젠 겁나​지 안하
ijen geopna​ji anha
... the things I used to fear
It's time to see what I can do
어딕카​지 할수 이쓸까
eodikka​ji halsu isseulkka
How far can I go?
To test the limits and break through
내 늤력 화긴 하고 파
nae neungryeok hwagin hago pa
I want to test my abilities
No right, no wrong, no rules for me
내 맘대로 자유럽게
nae mamdaero jayureopge
I'll live the way I want
I'm free!
살래
sallae
Freely!
Let it go, let it go!
다 잊어 다 잊어
da ijeo da ijeo
Forget it all, forget it all!
I am one with the wind and sky
한을 바람과 살테야
haneul baramgwa salteya
I'll live with the sky and the wind
Let it go, let it go!
다 잊어 다 잊어
da ijeo da ijeo
Forget it all, forget it all!
You'll never see me cry
이​제 다시 울지 안흘l애
i​je dasi ulji anheullae
Now, I'll never cry again
Here I stand, and here I'll stay,
당당히 사라갈l애
dangdanghi saragallae
I'll live proudly
Let the storm rage on...
폭풌 모라쳐도
pokpung morachyeodo
Though the storm rages on...
My power flurries through the air and to the ground
내 힘은 눈보라로 세샀을 덥고
nae himeun nunboraro sesangeul deopgo
My power covers the world with a blizzard
My soul is spiralling in frozen fractals all around
내 였혼 휘​모라치​며 꽀꽀 어려버리​네
nae yeonghon hwi​morachi​myeo kkongkkong eoryeobeori​ne
My soul swirls, freezing everything around
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
내 마​은 가​는대로 모두 어름돼
nae ma​eun ga​neundaero modu eoreumdwae
Freeze everything to my liking
I'm never going back
도라가​지 안흘l애
doraga​ji anheullae
I'm not going back
The past is in the past!
과거​는 과거야
gwageo​neun gwageoya
The past is in the past!
Let it go, let it go!
다 잊어 다 잊어
da ijeo da ijeo
Forget it all, forget it all!
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
이​제 다시 일어설 거야
i​je dasi ileoseol geoya
Now I rise up again
Let it go, let it go!
다 잊어 다 잊어
da ijeo da ijeo
Forget it all, forget it all!
That perfect girl is gone
착핻던 그 손여
chakhaetdeon geu sonyeo
That girl who was nice
Here I stand in the light of day
당당히 살아가리라
dangdanghi salagarira
I'll live proudly
Let the storm rage on!
폭풌 몰아쳐도
pokpung molachyeodo
Though the storm rages on...
The cold never bothered me anyway.
추위 따윈 두렵지 않다​네
chuwi ttawin duryeopji anda​ne
I'm not afraid of the cold.